이웃한테 잘해주는 건 좋은데요
I know you think you're being generous,
선물을 주고받는 행위는 상호적인 데 기반을 두고 있어요
but the foundation of gift-giving is reciprocity.
페니는 나한테 선물을 주는 게 아니라 의무를 주는 거예요
You haven't given me a gift. You've given me an obligation.
기분 나빠하지 마요 쉘든한테 누구나 하는 실수예요
Don't feel bad, Penny, it's a classic rookie mistake.
쉘든과 처음 하누카를 보낼 때는 8일 내내 저한테 소리쳤거든요
My first Hanukah with Sheldon, he yelled at me for eight nights.
전 선물 안 받아도 상관없어요
You don't have to get me anything in return.
당연히 줘야죠
Of course I do.
선물 주고받는 행위의 본질에 따르면 나한테 준 선물과 같은 우정의 정도를 나타내는
The essence of the custom is that I now have to go out and purchase for you
선물이나 물적 가치를 내가 사야 한다는 거죠
and representing the same perceived level of friendship